YICHI ZHANG

+1(734)800-6032 ♦ yichiz@umich.edu ♦ Website: https://yichiz97.github.io/ 4352 North Quad, 510 State St., Ann Arbor, MI 48109, U.S.A.

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Information elicitation, mechanism design, incentive-aware learning and decision making, problems at the interface of AI and economics. Applications of interest include crowdsourcing, peer review, peer grading, recommender systems, and generative AI. My recent research interest is centered around utilizing large language models to elicit and aggregate text-based human responses, e.g. in peer review.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Umich)

Sep 2019 - Present

- Ph.D. in School of Information
- Advisor: Grant Schoenebeck
- Thesis: Incentive Design for Data-driven Systems: Effort and Information Elicitation

Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU)

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

- B.S. in Electronic Science and Engineering
- Advisor: Xinbing Wang and Luoyi Fu

WORKING EXPERIENCES

University of Michigan, School of Information Research Assistant, Useful Theory Innovation Lab	Sep 2019 - Present
UCLA, Department of Computer Science Research Intern, working with Mario Gerla	Jul 2018 - Sep 2018
YITUTech Algorithm Engineer Intern	Feb 2019 - May 2019

SUBMISSIONS UNDER REVIEW

Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review Yichi Zhang, Grant Schoenebeck and Weijie Su

Understanding When Peer Grades (Definitely) Outperform Instructor Grades Noah Burrell, Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

Spot Check Equivalence: a Metric of an Information Elicitation Mechanism's Motivational Proficiency

Shengwei Xu, Grant Schoenebeck, Yichi Zhang and Paul Resnick

PUBLICATIONS

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

Grant Schoenebeck, Fang-Yi Yu and Yichi Zhang (ranked by alphabet)

In Proceedings of the 30th Annual World Wide Web Conference

(WWW 2021)

[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3449840]

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

Yichi Zhang, Fang-Yi Yu, Grant Schoenebeck and David Kempe

In Proceedings of the 23rd ACM Conference on Economics and Computation

 $(EC \ 2022)$

[https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09020]

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference

(WWW 2023)

[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583334]

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference [https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583292]

(WWW 2023)

[100] 507 / 411401111018/ 401/ 400/ 1011110/ 00

POSTERS

Eliciting Effort And Truth-telling From Parties of (No) Interest

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)
- U-M Asian American Faculty & Student Accomplishments Symposium (2022)

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

- DIMACS Workshop on Forecasting (2021)
- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2021)

SELECTED TALKS

Improving Conference Review Via Mechanism Design

• Renmin University of China, Gaoling School of Artificial Intelligence	August 2023
• Peking University, CFCS seminar	July 2023
• University of Michigan, DSCSS seminar	April 2023
• University of Pennsylvania, Wharton Statistics and Data Science	March 2023

TEACHING

Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Winter 2022

Courses: Big Data Analysis (SI 699)

Instructor: Misha Teplitskiy

Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Fall 2021

Course: Deep Learning (SIADS 642) Instructor: Paramveer Dhillon

Course: Network Analysis (SIADS 642)

Instructor: Daniel Romero

AWARDS

• The Web Conference Student Scholarship.	2021
• Outstanding Graduate of Shanghai Jiao Tong University.	2019
• EIC Education Scholarship (top 5%).	2018
• Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).	2017

SERVICE

Reviewer/PC member:

- The Web Conference (WWW): 2024, 2023, 2022
- Economics and Computation (EC): 2023, 2022
- Web and Internet Economics (WINE): 2023